

Rozhiar Omer

Frontend Web Developer

My Contacts

🛇 🛮 Sulaymanyah, Iraq

rozhiarrashid@gmail.com

(+964 771 020 7959

(in) /Rozhiar Rashid/(C)Rozhiar-tech

Technical Skills

HTML css JavaScript **Tailwind** React Bootstrap **Flutter** Dart **Firebase** Next.js **Python**

Projects

Happy- DEMO | CODE

Dec 2022 - Jan 2023 /Full Time

A platform where all middle east can easily find a therapist

JavaScript, React, Firebase, Tailwind

Project Lead handled Frontend and some of the backend as well Used for better performance

Popcorn Store - DEMO | CODE

Nov 2022 - Dec 2022 /Full Time

A place for everyone to pick a movie based on there needs

JavaScript , HTML, Css, Tailwind Handled everything related to the FrontEnd Fething API data organize them

Soft Skill

- Observation
- Decision makina
- Communication
- Multi-tasking
- TeamWork

Languages

- Native Kurdish
- English Full Professional Proficiency. Arabic Limited Working Proficiency

About Me

Hi there! My name is Rozhiar and I am a frontend developer with 2 years of experience building web applications. I am passionate about creating intuitive and visually appealing user interfaces, and I enjoy learning about new technologies and techniques to improve my skills.

Professional Experience

Mobile Application Developer- RozhGroup

Feb 2020 - Jun 20221 /Full Time

- · Designing and developing mobile applications for iOS and/or Android platforms.
- Writing clean, maintainable, and efficient code.

 Collaborating with designers and other team members to develop intuitive and visually appealing user interfaces.
- Ensuring that your code is optimized for performance, security, and accessibility.
- Debugging and fixing issues with mobile applications
- Ensuring that your code adheres to coding standards and best practices.

Lab assistant- University of Human Development

- Providing technical support to students and faculty using the lab's computer systems and equipment
- Maintaining and troubleshooting computer hardware and software issues.
- Installing and configuring software and operating systems.
 Assisting with the maintenance and upkeep of the lab's inventory of computers and other equipment.
- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$. Assisting with the setup and management of network infrastructure, including switches, routers, and servers.
- Providing support for online learning platforms and tools.
 Assisting with the development and maintenance of websites and other online resources.

Frontend Developer- Mazee advertisement

- Designing and implementing user-facing features for web and mobile applications.
 Building and maintaining efficient, reusable, and reliable front-end code.
- Collaborating with designers and other team members to develop intuitive and visually
- Ensuring that the code you write is optimized for performance, security, and accessibility. Debugging and fixing issues with the front end of the web and mobile applications. Ensuring that your code adheres to coding standards and best practices.
- Staying up to date with new technologies and techniques in front-end development.
- Participating in code reviews and providing feedback to other team members Mentoring and guiding less experienced team members.
- Participating in the design and planning of new projects and features.

Frontend Web Development - Re:Coded

Feb 2020 - Jun 2022

Education

Re:Coded Immersive bootcamps are highly competitive, with a 5% acceptance rate.

- Completing a 4.5-month immersive design bootcamp, with 300+ hours of curricula and project-based learning
- Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React
- Working with various design teams to create products across industries.

Information Technology -University **Human Development**

Nov 2017 - may 2021

Completing a 4-years immersive design Courses, with 3600-5400 hours of curricula and project-based learning in all IT and CS courses